[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionText": "Which city has higghest poppulation in India ?",
    "questionAns": "Mumbai",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Ahemdabad", "Mumbai", "Delhi", "Surat"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionText": "Which is national animal of India ?",
    "questionAns": "Tiger",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Bear", "Fox", "Tiger", "Wolf"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionText": "Which is national bird of India ?",
    "questionAns": "Peacock",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Dove", "Falcon", "Parrot", "Peacock"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionText": "Which is state animal of Gujrat ?",
    "questionAns": "Lion",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Lion", "Leapoard", "Rino", "Jaquar"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionText": "Which is state bird of Gujrat ?",
    "questionAns": "Flamingo",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Owl", "Flamingo", "Sparrow", "Crow"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "questionText": "Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges?",
    "questionAns": "Narmada",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Narmada", "Mahanadi", "Tapi", "Mahi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "questionText": "The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?",
    "questionAns": "Cuttak",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Chennai", "Cuttak", "Banglore", "Quilon"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "questionText": "Who among the following wrote Sanskrit grammar?",
    "questionAns": "Panini",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Kalidas", "Charak", "Panini", "Aaryabhatt"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "questionText": "Which among the following headstreams meets the Ganges in last?",
    "questionAns": "Bhagirathi",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Alaknanda", "Pindar", "Mandakini", "Bhagirathi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "questionText": "The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is?",
    "questionAns": "Silver",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Zinc", "Silver", "Copper", "Aluminium"]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "questionText": "Which one of the following rivers originates in Brahmagiri range of Western Ghats?",
    "questionAns": "Cauvery",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Pennar", "Cauvery", "Krishna", "Tapi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "questionText": "The country that has the highest in Barley Production?",
    "questionAns": "Russia",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["China", "India", "Russia", "France"]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "questionText": "Tsunamis are not caused by",
    "questionAns": "Hurricanes",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Hurricanes",
      "Earthquakes",
      "Undersea landslides",
      "Volcanic eruptions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "questionText": "Chambal river is a part of –",
    "questionAns": "Narmada basin",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Sabarmati basin",
      "Ganga basin",
      "Narmada basin",
      "Godavari basin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "questionText": "Volcanic eruption do not occur in the",
    "questionAns": "Baltic sea",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Baltic sea", "Black sea", "Caribbean sea", "Caspian sea"]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "questionText": "Indus river originates in –",
    "questionAns": "Tibet",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Kinnaur", "Ladakh", "Nepal", "Tibet"]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "questionText": "The hottest planet in the solar system?",
    "questionAns": "Venus",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Mercury", "Venus", "Mars", "Jupiter"]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "questionText": "With which of the following rivers does Chambal river merge?",
    "questionAns": "Yamuna",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Banas", "Ganga", "Narmada", "Yamuna"]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "questionText": "Where was the electricity supply first introduced in India –",
    "questionAns": "Darjeeling",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Mumbai", "Dehradun", "Darjeeling", "Chennai"]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "questionText": "Which peninsular river is least seasonal in flow?",
    "questionAns": "Godavari",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Narmada", "Krishna", "Godavari", "Cauvery"]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "questionText": " Which animal is known as the 'Ship of the Desert'?",
    "questionAns": "Camel",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Horse", "Camel", "Dog", "Cat"]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "questionText": "How many days are there in a week?",
    "questionAns": "7",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["5", "6", "7", "4"]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "questionText": "How many hours are there in a day?",
    "questionAns": "24",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["22", "21", "23", "24"]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "questionText": "How many letters are there in the English alphabet?",
    "questionAns": "26",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["26", "24", "23", "22"]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "questionText": "Rainbow consist of how many colours?",
    "questionAns": "7",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["4", "7", "5", "6"]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "questionText": "How many minutes are there in an hour?",
    "questionAns": "60 min",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["60 min", "50 min", "40 min", "45 min"]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "questionText": "How many seconds make one hour?",
    "questionAns": "3600",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["3500", "3600", "3400", "3100"]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "questionText": "Baby frog is known as.......",
    "questionAns": "Tadpole",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Kitten", "Pony", "Tadpole", "Turtle"]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "questionText": "How many consonants are there in the English alphabet?",
    "questionAns": "21",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["20", "26", "24", "21"]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "questionText": "How many vowels are there in the English alphabet and name them?",
    "questionAns": "5",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["4", "5", "3", "2"]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "questionText": "Which animal is known as the king of the jungle?",
    "questionAns": "Lion",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Bear", "Lion", "Wolf", "Rino"]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "questionText": "Name the national flower of India?",
    "questionAns": "Lotus",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Rose", "Jasmine", "Lotus", "Lili"]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "questionText": "Name the National fruit of India?",
    "questionAns": "Mango",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Mango", "Apple", "Orange", "Kiwi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "questionText": "Name the National game of India?",
    "questionAns": "Hockey",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Cricket", "Chess", "Hockey", "Kabbadi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "questionText": "Name the National tree of India?",
    "questionAns": "Banyan tree",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Banyan tree", "Neem tree", "Ashoka tree", "Mango tree"]
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "questionText": "Name the National river of India?",
    "questionAns": "Ganga",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Narmada", "Tapi", "Jelam", "Ganga"]
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "questionText": "What is the capital of India?",
    "questionAns": "New Delhi",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Ahemdabad", "New Delhi", "Mumbai", "Varansi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "questionText": "Name the biggest continent in the world?",
    "questionAns": "Asia",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Africa", "Australia", "North America", "Asia"]
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "questionText": "How many continents are there in the world?",
    "questionAns": "7",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["4", "6", "7", "5"]
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "questionText": "Which is the smallest month of the year?",
    "questionAns": "February",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["March", "June", "February", "July"]
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "questionText": "Which colour symbolises peace?",
    "questionAns": "White",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Red", "White", "Black", "Blue"]
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "questionText": "Name the largest mammal?",
    "questionAns": "Blue Whale",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Elephant", "Rino", "Blue Whale", "Human"]
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "questionText": "Sun rises in the.....",
    "questionAns": "East",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["East", "West", "North", "South"]
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "questionText": "How many sides are there in a triangle?",
    "questionAns": "Three",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"]
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "questionText": "Who is the first citizen of India?",
    "questionAns": "The President of India",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "The President of India",
      "The Prime Minister of India",
      "The State Governer of India",
      "Army Officer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "questionText": "How many states are there in India?",
    "questionAns": "28",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["21", "26", "27", "28"]
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "questionText": "How many Union Territories are there in India?",
    "questionAns": "8",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["7", "8", "6", "5"]
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "questionText": "How many years are there in one Millenium?",
    "questionAns": "1000",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["100", "10", "10000", "1000"]
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "questionText": "Name the first man to walk on the Moon?",
    "questionAns": "Neil Armstrong",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Mitesh Chavda",
      "Dhruv Patel",
      "Neil Armstrong",
      "Purvesh Thakkar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "questionText": "Which festival is called the festival of colours?",
    "questionAns": "Holi",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Assam", "Uttarayan", "Holi", "Cristmas"]
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "questionText": "What type of gas is absorbed by plants?",
    "questionAns": "co2",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["o2", "co2", "o3", "co"]
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "questionText": "How many days a February month have in the leap year?",
    "questionAns": "29",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["28", "30", "29", "31"]
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "questionText": "Name the longest river on the Earth?",
    "questionAns": "Nile",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Nile", "Ganga", "Tapi", "Sabarmati"]
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "questionText": "Which festival is known as the festival of light?",
    "questionAns": "Diwali",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Holi", "Diwali", "Uttarayan", "Gudi Padwa"]
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "questionText": "Name a bird that lays the largest eggs?",
    "questionAns": "Ostrich",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Ostrich", "Peacock", "Crow", "Eagle"]
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "questionText": "Name the National Heritage Animal of India?",
    "questionAns": "Elephant",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Tiger", "Lion", "Rino", "Elephant"]
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "questionText": "Who invented Radio?",
    "questionAns": "Guglielmo Marconi",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Dhruv Patel",
      "Guglielmo Marconi",
      "Mitesh Chavda",
      "Purvesh Thakkar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "questionText": "Name the planet known as the Red Planet?",
    "questionAns": "Mars",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Earth", "Jupiter", "Mercury", "Mars"]
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "questionText": "Who is the first woman prime minister of India?",
    "questionAns": "Indira Gandhi",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Margi Trivedi",
      "Mandeep Saini",
      "Indira Gandhi",
      "Supriya Kumari"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "questionText": "Name the National game of the USA?",
    "questionAns": "Baseball",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Cricket", "Hockey", "Baseball", "Chess"]
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "questionText": "Who invented Watch?",
    "questionAns": "Peter Henlein",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Meet Patel", "Peter Henlein", "Price Patel", "Siddharth Patel"]
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "questionText": "Name the largest 'Democracy' of the world?",
    "questionAns": "India",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Russia", "Australia", "India", "England"]
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "questionText": "Name the country known as the Land of the Rising Sun?",
    "questionAns": "Japan",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["India", "U.S.A", "U.K", "Japan"]
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "questionText": "How many millimetres are there in a centimetre?",
    "questionAns": "10",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["10", "100", "1000", "1"]
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "questionText": "Name the hardest substance available on Earth?",
    "questionAns": "Dimond",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Gold", "Dimond", "Silver", "Glass"]
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "questionText": "Name a shape that has ten sides?",
    "questionAns": "Decagon",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Decagon", "Triangle", "Circle", "Square"]
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "questionText": "Name the largest ocean in the World?",
    "questionAns": "Pacific",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Arctic", "Pacific", "Indian", "Atlantic"]
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "questionText": "Who is the real founder of Microsoft?",
    "questionAns": "Bill Gates",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Elon Musk", "Warren Buffet", "Bill Gates", "Gautam Adani"]
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "questionText": "Who gave the theory of Relativity?",
    "questionAns": "Albert Einstein",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Issac Newton", "Greham Bell", "Dhruv Patel", "Albert Einstein"]
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "questionText": "Who discovered the X-rays first?",
    "questionAns": "Wilhelm Roentgen",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Wilhelm Roentgen",
      "Issac Newton",
      "Greham Bell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "questionText": "Who gave the universal law of gravitation?",
    "questionAns": "Issac Newton",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Issac Newton",
      "Wilhelm Roentgen",
      "Greham Bell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "questionText": "Name a natural satellite of Earth?",
    "questionAns": "Moon",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Sun", "Moon", "Aaryabhatt", "Jupiter"]
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "questionText": "Which bird is known for its intelligence?",
    "questionAns": "Owl ",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Owl ", "Sparrow", "Eagle", "Crow"]
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "questionText": "Which country are the Giza Pyramids in?",
    "questionAns": "Egypt",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["India", "Nepal", "Egypt", "Norway"]
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "questionText": "What city is the statue of liberty in?",
    "questionAns": "New York",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["New York", "Tempa", "Winter Heaven", "Chicago"]
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "questionText": "How many Cricket world cups does India have?",
    "questionAns": "2",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["3", "4", "5", "2"]
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "questionText": "Gir National Park in Gujarat is famous for?",
    "questionAns": "Lion",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Deer", "Lion", "Bear", "Tiger"]
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "questionText": "Brain of computer is?",
    "questionAns": "CPU",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Moniter", "Keyboard", "Mouse", "CPU"]
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "questionText": "Giddha is the folk dance of?",
    "questionAns": "Punjab",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Goa", "Gujrat", "Punjab", "Rajasthan"]
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "questionText": "1024 Kilobytes is equal to?",
    "questionAns": "1mb",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["1gb", "1kb", "1mb", "1pb"]
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "questionText": "Smallest state of India is?",
    "questionAns": "Goa",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Goa", "Gujrat", "Punjab", "Rajasthan"]
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "questionText": "Fastest animal on earth is?",
    "questionAns": "Cheetah",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Elephant", "Rino", "Cheetah", "Lion"]
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "questionText": " A figure with 8 sides is called?",
    "questionAns": "Octagon",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Octagon", "Triangle", "Circle", "Square"]
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "questionText": "Most widely spoken language in the world is?",
    "questionAns": "Chinese",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Hindi", "Gujrati", "Chinese", "Marathi"]
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "questionText": "Which organ purify our blood?",
    "questionAns": "Kidney",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Kidney", "Lungs", "Liver", "Heart"]
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "questionText": "How many colours are there in India’s National Flag?",
    "questionAns": "3",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["5", "1", "2", "3"]
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "questionText": "Gateway of India is located at?",
    "questionAns": "Mumbai",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Goa", "Mumbai", "Delhi", "Nadiad"]
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "questionText": "How many players are there in a cricket team?",
    "questionAns": "11",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["100", "10", "12", "11"]
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "questionText": "LBW is related to which sports?",
    "questionAns": "Cricket",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Chess", "Carrom", "Cricket", "Base ball"]
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "questionText": "Saina Nehwal is associated with which sports?",
    "questionAns": "Badminton",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Chess", "Cricket", "Badminton", "Carrom"]
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "questionText": "Olylmpics games are held after every?",
    "questionAns": "4 years",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["2 years", "4 years", "3 years", "5 years"]
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "questionText": "Which country does the company Sony come from?",
    "questionAns": "Japan",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["India", "China", "Japan", "Nepal"]
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "questionText": "In which season we wear warm clothes?",
    "questionAns": "Winter",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Winter", "Summer", "Monsoon", "Spring"]
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "questionText": "Which place is known as tea garden of India",
    "questionAns": "Assam",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Assam", "Kurg", "Charotar", "Dehradun"]
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "questionText": "Which is India’s largest fresh water lake?",
    "questionAns": "Wular Lake",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Wular Lake", "Dal Lake", "Sambhar lake", "Narki Lake"]
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "questionText": "How many primary colors are there?",
    "questionAns": "3",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["2", "5", "4", "3"]
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "questionText": "Which is the tallest animal on the earth?",
    "questionAns": "Giraffe",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Elephant",
      "Giraffe",
      "Cow",
      "Dog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "questionText": "What is the top color in a rainbow?",
    "questionAns": "Red",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Blue", "White", "Green", "Red"]
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "questionText": "Which festival is known as the ‘Festival of flowers’?",
    "questionAns": "Onam",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": [
      "Diwali",
      "Holi",
      "Onam",
      "Uttarayan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "questionText": "Which is the world’s largest flower?",
    "questionAns": "Rafflesia",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["Lotus", "Rose", "Rafflesia", "Lili"]
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "questionText": "How many zeros are there in one hundred thousand?",
    "questionAns": "5",
    "selectedOption": "Meet",
    "options": ["7", "5", "4", "8"]
  }
]
